

## Tiafau Purcell

- Web & Mobile UX/UI Designer
- www.tiafaupurcell.me | www.verdadtech.com
- tiafaupurcell03@gmail.com | tiafau@verdadtech.com
- **4** 808.203.9160

Focused on designing creative solutions that promote user adoption and ease of use to support the business needs. Working knowledge of front end design and development practices. Follows user-centered design process through research analysis, ideation, information architecture, wireframing, prototyping, interaction and interface design, and implementation and iteration.

## Skills

Information architecture, wireframing, prototyping, interaction design, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Adobe suite, Bootstrap framework, graphic design, print design, logo design, web and mobile design.

## Experience

Design Engineer @ Verdad Technologies 06/2015 to current in Provo, UT

Web and mobile UX/UI and front-end development for software company

Co-founder @ Sweep the Earth 11/2014 to current in Provo, UT

Lead designer and product development for web and mobile app company

UX/UI Designer @ Smart Rhino Labs 11/2013 to 04/2015 in Draper, UT

Design user experiences for our 20+ recruitment marketing sites

## Education

iOS/Web Development @ DevMountain 2014 to 2014 in Provo, UT

12-week intensive course in iOS and web development (24 weeks total)

Web Design and Development @ Full Sail University (Online) 2012 to 2013 in Provo, UT

Latin American Studies, BA @ Brigham Young University 2004 to 2011 in Provo, UT